BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10)
1950-1976
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS)
6178/010
39 cubic feet
39 linear ft.
Records (documents), collective labor agreements.
5833611
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, July 12, 2005
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 21, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The US Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) was established in 1884 to collect information about employment and labor in the United States. As mandated by the 1947 Taft-Hartley Act, the BLS was formally tasked with responsibility for soliciting, collecting, and analyzing collective bargaining agreements (CBAs) from public and private establishments, and making the agreements publicly available. In the early 1980s, this was function was limited to union contracts made with employers of 1000 or more employees.
In 2002, the National Archives and Records Administration authorized the BLS to donate inactive, non-confidential agreements which were 5 years or more past their expiration date to the Kheel Center where they would be preserved and made available to the public. The Office of Labor-Management Services took over responsibility for collecting and analyzing CBAs in 2011, and continues this donor relationship with the Kheel Center.
Scope and Contents
The US Department of Labor Historical Collective Bargaining Agreements Collection, 6178, is made up of 21 series of expired public- and private-sector collective bargaining agreements dating from 1887 to 2003 and totals 685 linear feet plus 10 CDs of digitized documents and 320 reels of microfilm. In addition to the CBAs, a small volume of related documents such as union constitutions, pension and health plans submitted to the BLS, are also available.
Selected collective bargaining agreements from this collection were digitized with generous funding from the National Historic Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC), and the National Science Foundation (NSF). Because documents other than collective bargaining agreements were also collected and preserved here by the US Department of Labor, a folder containing material that has been digitized, may also contain material which has not been digitized such as constitutions, bylaws, working rules, life insurance plans, or other organizational documents. For access to non-digitized material, contact Kheel Center staff.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/023: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
Arrangement
Series I: Industry Code #21, Mining, Quarrying, and Oil and Gas Extraction
Series II: Industry Code #22, Utilities
Series III: Industry Code #23, Construction
Series IV: Industry Code #31, Manufacturing
Series V: Industry Code #32, Manufacturing
Series VI: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
Series VII: Industry Code #42, Wholesale Trade
Series VIII: Industry Code #44, Retail Trade
Series IX: Industry Code #45, Retail Trade
Series X: Industry Code #48, Transportation and Warehousing
Series XI: Industry Code #49, Transportation and Warehousing
Series XII: Industry Code #51, Information
Series XIII: Industry Code #52, Finance and Insurance
Series XIV: Industry Code #54, Professional, Scientific, and Technical Services
Series XV: Industry Code #56, Administrative and Support and Waste Management and Remediation Services
Series XVI: Code #62, Health Care and Social Assistance
Series XVII: Code #72, Accommodation and Food Services
Series XVIII: Code #81, Other Services (except Public Administration)
Industrial relations -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- United States; Labor unions -- United States; United States. Department of Labor -- Archives; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics -- Archives; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics. Division of Industrial Relations -- Archives; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics. Office of Wages and Industrial Relations-- Archives
5833611
- Series I: Industry Code #21, Mining, Quarrying, and Oil and Gas Extraction
  - Code no.8313: Coal Producers and UMW, 1958-1964 (Box 36, Folder 8373)
- Series II: Industry Code #22, Utilities
  - Code no.6000: Alabama Power Company and IBEW, 1961-1966 (Box 20, Folder 6000)
  - Code no.6001: Arizona Public Service Co. and IBEW Local 387, 1961-1969 (Box 20, Folder 6001)
  - Code no.6004: Bonneville Power Administration and Columbia Power Trades Council, 1961-1963 (Box 20, Folder 6004)
  - Code no.6008: Public Service Company of Commonwealth Edison Company and IBEW, 1959-1969 (Box 20, Folder 6008)
  - Code no.6009: Commonwealth Edison Company and IBEW Locals 1359, 1366, 1367, 1399, 1959-1969 (Box 20, Folder 6009)
  - Code no.6010: Commonwealth Edison Company and IBEW Local 1427, 1959-1965 (Box 20, Folder 6010)
  - Code no.6011: Public Service Company of Commonwealth Edison Company and IBEW Locals 1530, 1539, 1540, 1557, 1959- 1969 (Box 21, Folder 6011)
  - Code no.6012: Duquense Light Company and IBEW Locals 140, 142, 144, 147, 148, 1960-1966 (Box 21, Folder 6012)
  - Code no.6013: Florida Power Corporation and IBEW, 1958-1966 (Box 21, Folder 6013)
  - Code no.6014: Florida Power and Light Company and IBEW, 1960-1967 (Box 21, Folder 6014)
  - Code no.6016: Houston Lighting Power Company and IBEW, 1960-1968 (Box 21, Folder 6016)
  - Code no.6018: Iowa Power and Light Company and IBEW Local 499, 1960-1967 (Box 21, Folder 6018)
  - Code no.6019: Kansas Power and Light Company and IBEW Local 304, 1961-1965 (Box 21, Folder 6019)
  - Code no.6020: Metropolitan Edison Company and IBEW Locals 563, 603, 803, 1261, 1482, 1961-1970 (Box 21, Folder 6020)
  - Code no.6021: Narragansett Electric Company and International Brotherhood of Utility Workers of New England Locals 310, 314, 1960- 1972 (Box 21, Folder 6021)
  - Code no.6023: Ohio Edison Company and Utility Workers Union of America Locals 126, 177, 181, 350, 351, 353, 1960-1966 (Box 21, Folder 6023)
  - Code no.6024: Pennsylvania Electric Company and IBEW, 1960-1968 (Box 21, Folder 6024)
  - Code no.6027: Public Service Electric and Gas Company and IBEW, 1961-1968 (Box 21, Folder 6027)
  - Code no.6029: Puget Sound Power and Light Company and IBEW Local 77, 1963-1970 (Box 21, Folder 6029)
  - Code no.6036: Union Electric Company and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 148, 1960-1971 (Box 21, Folder 6036)
  - Code no.6037: United Illuminating Company and Federation of Utility Employees, 1960-1968 (Box 21, Folder 6037)
  - Code no.6038: Utah Power and Light Company and IBEW Local 57, 1961-1967 (Box 22, Folder 6038)
  - Code no.6039: West Penn Power Company and Utility Workers Union of America Local 102, 1956-1970 (Box 22, Folder 6039)
  - Code no.6040: Wisconsin Electric Power Company and IBEW Local 494, 1963-1971 (Box 22, Folder 6040)
  - Code no.6042: Boston Gas Company and UMW Local 12003, 1961-1967 (Box 22, Folder 6042)
  - Code no.6050: Southern California Gas Company and Utility Workers Union of America Locals 132, 170, 243, 1961-1969 (Box 22, Folder 6050)
  - Code no.6051: Southern Counties Gas Company of California and International Chemical Workers Union Local 527, 1961-1970 (Box 22, Folder 6051)
  - Code no.6064: Jersey Central Power and Light Company and IBEW Locals 1289, 1298, 1303, 1309, 1314, 1960-1969 (Box 22, Folder 6064)
  - Code no.6068: Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation and IBEW, 1961-1968 (Box 22, Folder 6068)
  - Code no.6074: Peoples Gas Light and Coke Company and Gas Workers Union Local 18007, 1961-1969 (Box 22, Folder 6074)
  - Code no.6076: Public Service Electric and Gas Company and Utility Coworkers Association, 1961-1967 (Box 22, Folder 6076)
  - Code no.6077: San Diego Gas and Electric Company and IBEW Local 465, 1963-1969 (Box 22, Folder 6077)
  - Code no. 6079: Virginia Electric and Power Company and IBEW Local 216, 220, 279, 655, 699, 905, 980, 1064, 1964-1971 (Box 22, Folder 6079)
  - Code no.6080: Wisconsin Power and Light Company and IBEW Local 965, 1961-1972 (Box 23, Folder 6080)
  - Code no.1619: Union Carbide Nuclear Company and Atomic Trades and Labor Council Local 480, 1961-1968 (Box 25, Folder 1619)
  - Code no.6002: Arkansas Power and Light Company and IBEW Locals 647, 1703, 750, 1962-1967 (Box 34, Folder 6002)
  - Code no.6003: Atlantic City Electric Company and IBEW Local 210, 1960-1967 (Box 34, Folder 6003)
  - Code no.6005: Boston Edison Company and Utility Workers Union of America Local 369, 1961-1967 (Box 34, Folder 6005)
  - Code no.6007: Cleveland Electric Illuminating Company and Utility Workers Union of America Local 270, 1960-1968 (Box 34, Folder 6007)
  - Code no.6015: Georgia Power Company and IBEW Locals 822, 84, 923, 780, 896, 847, 511, 1960-1965 (Box 34, Folder 6015)
  - Code no.6019: Kansas Power and Light Company and IBEW Local 304, 1965-1970 (Box 34, Folder 6019)
  - Code no.6022: Northern States Power Company, Minneapolis Division and IBEW Local 160, 1961-1973 (Box 34, Folder 6022)
  - Code no.6025: Pennsylvania Power and Light Company and Employees Independent Association, 1961-1970 (Box 34, Folder 6025)
  - Code no.6026: Potomac Electric Power Company and Electric Utility Employees' Union of Washington, D.C., 1960-1968 (Box 34, Folder 6026)
  - Code no.6028: Public Service Company of Indiana, Inc. and IBEW Local 1393, 1961-1969 (Box 34, Folder 6028)
  - Code no.6030: Southern California Edison Company and IBEW Local 47, 1960-1968 (Box 34, Folder 6030)
  - Code no.6034: Union Electric Company and IBEW Locals 309, 649, 1439, 1960-1963 (Box 34, Folder 6034)
  - Code no.6035: Union Electric Company and IBEW Local 1455, 1960-1963 (Box 34, Folder 6035)
  - Code no.6041: Wisconsin Electric Power Company and United Association of Office, Sales and Technical Employees Local 2, 1961- 1970 (Box 34, Folder 6041)
  - Code no.6043: Brooklyn Union Gas Company and Transport Workers Union of America Local 101, 1961-1971 (Box 35, Folder 6043)
  - Code no.6044: East Ohio Gas Company and Natural Gas Workers Union, 1960-1969 (Box 35, Folder 6044)
  - Code no.6045: Hope Natural Gas Company and Employees' Independent Union, 1961-1965 (Box 35, Folder 6045)
  - Code no.6045: River Gas Company and Employees' Independent Union, 1961-1965 (Box 35, Folder 6045)
  - Code no.6046: Iroquois Gas Corporation and UMW Local 12013, 1959-1975 (Box 35, Folder 6046)
  - Code no.6047: Laclede Gas Company and OCAW Locals 5-6, 8-6, 1960-1970 (Box 35, Folder 6047)
  - Code no.6048: Michigan Consolidated Gas Company and Gas Workers Union Local 80, 1960-1973 (Box 35, Folder 6048)
  - Code no.6054: Washington Gas Light Company and International Chemical Workers' Union Local 63, 1961-1970 (Box 35, Folder 6054)
  - Code no.6056: Cincinnati Gas and Electric Company and Independent Utilities Union, 1961-1967 (Box 35, Folder 6056)
  - Code no.6058: Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc. and Utility Workers' Union of America Local 1-2, 1959-1968 (Box 35, Folder 6058)
  - Code no.6059: Consumers Power Company and Utility Workers Union of America, 1960-1969 (Box 35, Folder 6059)
  - Code no.6060: Dayton Power and Light Company and Utility Workers of America Local 175, 1957-1970 (Box 35, Folder 6060)
  - Code no.6061: Detroit Edison Company and Utility Workers Union of America Local 223, 1961-1969 (Box 35, Folder 6061)
  - Code no.6062: Gulf States Utilities Company and Independent Electrical Workers Union, 1961-1968 (Box 35, Folder 6062)
  - Code no.6063: Illinois Power Company and IBEW Local 51, 1960-1964 (Box 35, Folder 6063)
  - Code no.6065: Long Island Lighting Company and IBEW Local 1049, 1958-1967 (Box 35, Folder 6065)
  - Code no.6066: Long Island Lighting Company and IBEW Local 1381, 1958-1965 (Box 35, Folder 6066)
  - Code no.6067: Louisville Gas and Electric Company and Independent Protective Association of Utility Workers, 1959-1967 (Box 35, Folder 6067)
  - Code no.6069: Northern Indiana Public Service Company and UMW Local 12775, 1959-1968 (Box 35, Folder 6069)
  - Code no.6070: New York State Electric and Gas Corporation and IBEW Locals 249, 945, 951, 961, 966, 992, 994, 1111, 1125, 1126, 1143, 1958-1967 (Box 35, Folder 6070)
- Series III: Industry Code #23, Construction
  - Code no.5771: Western Electric Company, Inc. and CWA, 1961-1967 (Box 20, Folder 5771)
  - Code no.5774: Western Electric Company, Inc. and CWA Local 9, 1962-1969 (Box 20, Folder 5774)
  - Code no.8418: Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and Building and Construction Trades Council of New Orleans and Vicinity, 1960-1968 (Box 24, Folder 8418)
  - Code no.8477: General Building Contractors Association, Inc. and International Union of Operating Engineers Locals 542, 542A, 542B, 1961-1971 (Box 24, Folder 8477)
  - Code no.8491: Association of General Contractors of America and Mobile Building and Construction Trades Council, 1961-1972 (Box 24, Folder 8491)
  - Code no.8508: Gulf Coast Piping Contractors Association and Pipefitters Local 195, 1960-1968 (Box 24, Folder 8508)
  - Code no.8508: Sabine Area Piping Contractors Association and Pipefitters Local 195, 1960-1968 (Box 24, Folder 8508)
  - Code no.8562: Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Local 1098 475, 1961- 1972 (Box 24, Folder 8562)
  - Code no.8567: Building Trades Employers Association of Syracuse and UBC Local 12, 1960-1970 (Box 24, Folder 8567)
  - Code no.8593: Connecticut Construction Industries Association, Inc. and Operating Engineers Local 478, 1964-1974 (Box 24, Folder 8593)
  - Code no.8689: Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and Construction and General Laborers Local 1177, 1963-1973 (Box 24, Folder 8689)
  - Code no.8538: San Francisco Electrical Contractors Association and IBEW Local 6, 1959-1971 (Box 36, Folder 8538)
  - Code no.8486: New England Road Builders' Association, Inc., Connecticut Labor Relations Division and International Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union of America, 1961-1973 (Box 36, Folder 8486)
  - Code no.8402: Southern California General Contractors and Operative Plasterers and Cement Masons International Association, 1957- 1970 (Box 36, Folder 8402)
  - Code no.8401: Southern California General Contractors and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1959- 1971 (Box 36, Folder 8401)
  - Code no.8539: Allied Construction Industries of Delaware, Inc. and International Hod Carriers and Common Laborers Union Locals 199 and 847 (Box 37, Folder 8539)
  - Code no.8540: Mason Contractors' Association of Milwaukee and Allied Construction Employers' Association, Inc., 1960-1968 (Box 37, Folder 8540)
  - Code no.8541: General Contractors of America, Miami Chapter and Bricklayers Union Local 7, 1964-1966 (Box 37, Folder 8541)
  - Code no.8542: Northern and Central California Chapter, Associated General Contractors and Northern California District Council of Hod Carriers, Building and Construction Laborers, 1960-1971 (Box 37, Folder 8542)
  - Code no.8543: Northern and Central California Chapter, Associated General Contractors and District Council of Plasterers and Cement Masons of Northern California, 1960-1971 (Box 37, Folder 8543)
  - Code no.8547: Builders' Association of Chicago and Cement Masons, Rock Asphalt and Composition Floor Finishers Local 502, 1960- 1963 (Box 37, Folder 8547)
  - Code no.8589: Associated General Contractors of Oklahoma, Chapter Builders Division and Carpenters Local Union Local 943, 1961- 1963 (Box 37, Folder 8549)
  - Code no.8549: Detroit Mason Contractor's Association and Metropolitan Executive Committee of Bricklayers, 1960-1968 (Box 37, Folder 8549)
  - Code no.8550: Employing Metallic Furring and Lathing Association of New York and Metallic Lathers' Union of New York and Vicinity Local 46, 1960-1963 (Box 37, Folder 8550)
  - Code no.8553: Mason Contractors Exchange of So. California and International Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union Locals 300, 439, 507, 652, 802, 806, 1082, 1960-1967 (Box 37, Folder 8553)
  - Code no.8554: Mason Contractor's Exchange of Southern California, Inc. and Bricklayers Union Locals 2, 13, 15, 26, 1960-1970 (Box 37, Folder 8554)
  - Code no.8555: Associated General Contractors of America, Detroit Chapter and Builders Association of Metropolitan Detroit, 1960- 1972 (Box 37, Folder 8555)
  - Code no.8559: Associated Building Contractors of Colorado, Inc. and Carpenters District Council of Denver and Vicinity, 1957- 1969 (Box 37, Folder 8559)
  - Code no.8560: Associated Contractors of Essex County, Inc. and Essex County and Vicinity District Council of Carpenters and Millwrights, 1960-1962 (Box 37, Folder 8560)
  - Code no.8563: Associated General Contractors of America, Inc., Rhode Island Chapter and Providence, Pawtucket and Central Falls Carpenters District Council of Carpenters and Joiners, 1960-1966 (Box 37, Folder 8563)
  - Code no.8564: Alaska Chapter, Associated Central Contractors, Inc. and Alaska Council of Carpenters, 1959-1969 (Box 37, Folder 8564)
  - Code no.8565: Associated General Contractors of St. Louis and St. Louis District Council, United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, 1957-1969 (Box 37, Folder 8565)
  - Code no.8566: Associated General Contractors of America, Inc., Cincinnati Chapter and Ohio Valley Carpenters' District Council, 1961- 1967 (Box 37, Folder 8566)
  - Code no.8569: General Building Contractors Association, Inc. and Metropolitan District Council of Philadelphia and Vicinity, United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, 1960-1963 (Box 37, Folder 8569)
  - Code no.8570: Madison Employers Council and Central Wisconsin District Council of Carpenters, 1961-1967 (Box 37, Folder 8570)
  - Code no.8572: Sheet Metal Roofing, Ventilating and Air Conditioning Contracting Divisions and Sheet Metal Workers International Association of Philadelphia Local 19, 1960-1962 (Box 37, Folder 8572)
  - Code no.8574: Sheet Metal Contractors Association of San Francisco and Sheet Metal Workers' International Association Local 104, 1960- 1965 (Box 37, Folder 8574)
  - Code no.8575: Sheet Metal Contractors Association of New York City and Sheet Metal Workers International Local 28, 1960- 1963 (Box 37, Folder 8575)
  - Code no.8576: Sheet Metal and Air Conditioning Contractors Association of Southern California, Inc. and Sheet Metal Workers International Union Local 108, 1957-1970 (Box 37, Folder 8576)
  - Code no.8577: Allied Building Metal Industries and Ironworkers Locals 40 and 361, 1960-1969 (Box 37, Folder 8577)
  - Code no.8580: Associated Steel Erectors of Chicago, Illinois and International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers Local 1, 1960-1969 (Box 37, Folder 8580)
  - Code no.8581: Excavators, Inc. and Excavating, Grading, Asphalt, Private Scavengers and Automobile Salesroom Attendants Local 731, 1966-1968 (Box 37, Folder 8581)
  - Code no.8581: Illinois Road Builders' Association and Excavating, Grading, Asphalt, Private Scavengers and Automobile Salesroom Attendants Local 731, 1966-1968 (Box 37, Folder 8581)
  - Code no.8581: Illinois Truck and Equipment Contractors Association and Excavating, Grading, Asphalt, Private Scavengers and Automobile Salesroom Attendants Local 731, 1966-1968 (Box 37, Folder 8581)
  - Code no.8582: Associated General Contractors of America, Northern and Central California Chapter and District Council of Iron Workers of the State of California and Vicinity, 1960-1965 (Box 37, Folder 8582)
  - Code no.8583: Ironworker Employers Association of Western Pennsylvania and International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Ironworkers of Pittsburgh, 1961-1970 (Box 37, Folder 8583)
  - Code no.8584: National Elevator Manufacturing, Inc. and International Union of Elevator Constructors, 1957-1966 (Box 37, Folder 8584)
  - Code no.8590: Floor Covering Association of Southern California, Inc. and Resilient Floor and Decorative Covering Local Union 1247, 1961-1970 (Box 37, Folder 8590)
  - Code no.8592: Northeastern States Boilermaker Employers and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, 1959-1970 (Box 37, Folder 8592)
  - Code no.8594: Master Builders' Association of Western Pennsylvania, Inc. and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 66, 1961- 1970 (Box 37, Folder 8594)
  - Code no.8596: Heavy Construction (Statewide Colorado) and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 9, 1959-1973 (Box 37, Folder 8596)
  - Code no.8598: Heating, Piping and Air Conditioning Contractors' Chicago Association and Pipe Fitters Association Local 597, 1957- 1962 (Box 37, Folder 8598)
  - Code no.8599: Wisconsin Road Builders Association and IBT Local 39, 1962-1966 (Box 37, Folder 8599)
  - Code no.8599: Wisconsin Road Builders Association and Operating Engineers Local 139, 1962-1966 (Box 37, Folder 8599)
  - Code no.8600: Electrical Contractors Association of Chicago and IBEW Local 134, 1962-1964 (Box 37, Folder 8600)
  - Code no.8601: Builders' Association of Chicago and Hoisting and Portable Engineers of Chicago Local 150, 1962-1973 (Box 37, Folder 8601)
  - Code no.8602: Associated General Contractors, Inc. Nevada Chapter and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 12, 1962- 1970 (Box 37, Folder 8602)
  - Code no.8609: Ventilating and Air Conditioning Contractors Association and Sheet Metal Workers Local 73, 1962-1968 (Box 37, Folder 8609)
  - Code no.8610: Refrigeration and Air Conditioning Contractors Association of Southern California, Inc. and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting Industry Local 250, 1962-1966 (Box 37, Folder 8610)
  - Code no.8612: Associated General Contractors of America, Georgia Branch and UBC Local 225, 1961-1973 (Box 37, Folder 8612)
  - Code no.8613: Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and UBC Local 101, 1963-1970 (Box 37, Folder 8613)